(Sheldon:)Well, that's not much of an apology,
but I'll take it.
(Leonard:)Excuse me.
(Leonard:)Is there anything you'd like
to apologize for?
Yes. Ahem.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry I tried to blow up your head.
(Sheldon:)It was uncalled for.
(Howard(entering with Raj):)You won't believe this.
(Raj:)Somebody got the whole thing
on their cell phone and put it on YouTube.
(Penny:)What?
- Now, who would do that?
- That would be me.
(Howard:)Check it out. It's a featured video.
You hit me. You saw that. He hit me.
- You tried to blow up my head.
- So it was working.
(Leonard:)- It was not... You are a nutcase.
- We'll see about that.
You people in the front row, heads up.
This is a splash zone.
Stop it. Quit it. Quit it.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- Hit you with a Vulcan nerve pinch.
- No pinches. No...!
You should clip your fingernails.
Those hurt.
(Leonard:)Oh, jeez.
Does this suit really look that bad?
(Sheldon:)Forget your suit.
Look at my arms waving.
(Sheldon:)I'm like a flamingo on Ritalin.
(Penny(entering):)Howard, would you like
to explain to me...
(Penny(entering):)...why your Facebook page has a picture
of me sleeping on your shoulder captioned:
"Me and my girlfriend"?
Uh-oh, here comes the talk.
(Sheldon:)- He hit me.
- You tried to blow up my head.
- So it was working.
- It was not... You are a nutcase.
(Sheldon:)We'll see about that.
[IN MANDARIN]